<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PU Parking App</string>

    <string name="vehiclenumber">Vehicle Number</string>
    <string name="imagepreview">Image Preview</string>
    <string name="detail">Vehicle Number</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="name">Name:  </string>
    <string name="location">Location:  </string>
    <string name="hindi">हिंदी</string>
    <string name="gujarati">ગુજરાતી</string>
    <string name="email">Email:  </string>
    <string name="call">CAll</string>
    <string name="entername">Enter The Name Here</string>
    <string name="phnumber1">Enter Phone Number 1</string>
    <string name="phnumber2">Enter Phone Number 2</string>
    <string name="emailenter">Enter The Email</string>
    <string name="locationenter">Enter The Location</string>
    <string name="SUBMIT">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="femildesc">An Engineer, Professor, Research scholar and Entrepreneur, who holds Master in Technology (M.Tech) degree in Information Technology from R.G.P.V Bhopal . He has a leadership quality and a very broad vision to cross the different paths. A restless soul who always love to experiment something new. His goal is to utilize his Education, Technical knowledge , Skill Set and Experiences to the Education and Research Arena.</string>

    <string name="rohitdesc">Worked productively with Product Team to understand requirements and business specifications around Portfolio Management, Analytics and Risk.

Effectively coded software(Application) changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.

Worked to solve complex problems using the latest in Mobile, and Web Technologies.

Developed and presented findings and solutions to audiences including senior executives and stakeholders.
    </string>

    <string name="prashantdesc">Experienced Assistant Professor with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Project Analysis, Android Development, HTML, and Leadership. Strong education professional with a Master of Technology - MTech focused in Computer</string>


</resources>